[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CC", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", ",", "VBG", ",", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "All of these years later, 40 years of drug war, would either of us have difficulty anywhere in the United States finding our former drug of choice within 45 minutes?", "question_tokens": ["All", "of", "these", "years", "later", ",", "40", "years", "of", "drug", "war", ",", "would", "either", "of", "us", "have", "difficulty", "anywhere", "in", "the", "United", "States", "finding", "our", "former", "drug", "of", "choice", "within", "45", "minutes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RBR", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "I think you and I could walk out of here and within about 90 seconds of yelling, looking, at least someone come toward us and probably somewhere within five minutes of that, probably west of here, we'd both be able to take care of whatever we needed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "and", "I", "could", "walk", "out", "of", "here", "and", "within", "about", "90", "seconds", "of", "yelling", ",", "looking", ",", "at", "least", "someone", "come", "toward", "us", "and", "probably", "somewhere", "within", "five", "minutes", "of", "that", ",", "probably", "west", "of", "here", ",", "we", "'d", "both", "be", "able", "to", "take", "care", "of", "whatever", "we", "needed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "So, David Carr, why do you think if we have had actual Hamsterdams, what would America look like or do we have them already?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "David", "Carr", ",", "why", "do", "you", "think", "if", "we", "have", "had", "actual", "Hamsterdams", ",", "what", "would", "America", "look", "like", "or", "do", "we", "have", "them", "already", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Part of the problem is drug addiction tends to be a serial matter and it's not easy to fix and people say treatment doesn't work, and in fact it doesn't.", "answer_tokens": ["Part", "of", "the", "problem", "is", "drug", "addiction", "tends", "to", "be", "a", "serial", "matter", "and", "it", "'s", "not", "easy", "to", "fix", "and", "people", "say", "treatment", "does", "n't", "work", ",", "and", "in", "fact", "it", "does", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Carr"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$300", "$600 million"]}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "$", "CD", "CC", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Six tons, whole sale value?", "question_tokens": ["Six", "tons", ",", "whole", "sale", "value", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "This is over $300 or $600 million.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "over", "$", "300", "or", "$", "600", "million", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "So these are all kilo blocks?", "question_tokens": ["So", "these", "are", "all", "kilo", "blocks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Yes, kilo blocks.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "kilo", "blocks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Do you have a problem with this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "problem", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, whenever I feel somebody's hands up my skirt I'm always sort of interested in what exactly they are trying to find up there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "whenever", "I", "feel", "somebody", "'s", "hands", "up", "my", "skirt", "I", "'m", "always", "sort", "of", "interested", "in", "what", "exactly", "they", "are", "trying", "to", "find", "up", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Well, what does metadata mean to you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "does", "metadata", "mean", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What does it mean to you, David Simon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", ",", "David", "Simon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, you know --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Simon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 154, "question": "-- misuse this information?", "question_tokens": ["--", "misuse", "this", "information", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "My concern is that --", "answer_tokens": ["My", "concern", "is", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Well, I mean, who knows more about you, the NSA or Amazon?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "who", "knows", "more", "about", "you", ",", "the", "NSA", "or", "Amazon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Tony, if they want --", "answer_tokens": ["Tony", ",", "if", "they", "want", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NSA"], "LOCATION": ["Amazon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "If you had to spend the rest of your life in Russia or Venezuela, where would you pick?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "to", "spend", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "in", "Russia", "or", "Venezuela", ",", "where", "would", "you", "pick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I've not been to either place.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "not", "been", "to", "either", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia", "Venezuela"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "I should try it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "should", "try", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Yes, yes, totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "You're not loving it, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "loving", "it", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Mario Batali, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Mario", "Batali", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "It depends.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mario Batali"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Deeply traumatizing experience and you certainly were a product of that system, and in fact you yourself, at some point in your career early on as a chef, well, you were a miserable son of a bitch yourself, weren't you, Mr. Ripert?", "question_tokens": ["Deeply", "traumatizing", "experience", "and", "you", "certainly", "were", "a", "product", "of", "that", "system", ",", "and", "in", "fact", "you", "yourself", ",", "at", "some", "point", "in", "your", "career", "early", "on", "as", "a", "chef", ",", "well", ",", "you", "were", "a", "miserable", "son", "of", "a", "bitch", "yourself", ",", "were", "n't", "you", ",", "Mr.", "Ripert", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Yes, I was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Ripert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "It's all peace and love?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "peace", "and", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Love and kiss and stuff like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Love", "and", "kiss", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Does -- does it matter?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "--", "does", "it", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, I certainly don't think you want to be serving cancerous food to your customers, if you know what that is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "want", "to", "be", "serving", "cancerous", "food", "to", "your", "customers", ",", "if", "you", "know", "what", "that", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "If they want to kill themselves with food, it's OK with you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "want", "to", "kill", "themselves", "with", "food", ",", "it", "'s", "OK", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Right, but not alcoholic, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "but", "not", "alcoholic", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "So you wouldn't cut them off?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "n't", "cut", "them", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ":", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "How are we going to -- how are we going to raise a giraffe or smoke terrorists out of their holes if we're -- we're too fat to squeeze in after it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "we", "going", "to", "--", "how", "are", "we", "going", "to", "raise", "a", "giraffe", "or", "smoke", "terrorists", "out", "of", "their", "holes", "if", "we", "'re", "--", "we", "'re", "too", "fat", "to", "squeeze", "in", "after", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Even with -- even with we were skinny, we were not doing a very good job at smoking the terrorists out of their holes.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "with", "--", "even", "with", "we", "were", "skinny", ",", "we", "were", "not", "doing", "a", "very", "good", "job", "at", "smoking", "the", "terrorists", "out", "of", "their", "holes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "So I should really -- I should have another piece of cake?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "should", "really", "--", "I", "should", "have", "another", "piece", "of", "cake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Have another piece of cake.", "answer_tokens": ["Have", "another", "piece", "of", "cake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "And where do you really start to get into offensive?", "question_tokens": ["And", "where", "do", "you", "really", "start", "to", "get", "into", "offensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I think 20 percent is pretty much the standard.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "20", "percent", "is", "pretty", "much", "the", "standard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "That said, when was the last time you got bad service?", "question_tokens": ["That", "said", ",", "when", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "got", "bad", "service", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I don't get bad service anywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "get", "bad", "service", "anywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What's in this cocktail?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "in", "this", "cocktail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "This is one-third gin, one-third sweet Italian vermouth and one-third campari.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "one-third", "gin", ",", "one-third", "sweet", "Italian", "vermouth", "and", "one-third", "campari", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "And how did we get to bologna (ph) anyway?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "did", "we", "get", "to", "bologna", "(", "ph", ")", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I think that's a little short to be quite frank.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "little", "short", "to", "be", "quite", "frank", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "...how would you respond?", "question_tokens": ["...", "how", "would", "you", "respond", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I would have brutally kicked his ass.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "brutally", "kicked", "his", "ass", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "I just think (ph) -- the real question is, what if your buddies put that on the internet?", "question_tokens": ["I", "just", "think", "(", "ph", ")", "--", "the", "real", "question", "is", ",", "what", "if", "your", "buddies", "put", "that", "on", "the", "internet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "(ph): Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "ph", ")", ":", "Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "It was one of his pals that were there, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "one", "of", "his", "pals", "that", "were", "there", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Pee (ph) in a bucket?", "question_tokens": ["Pee", "(", "ph", ")", "in", "a", "bucket", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "All right, last question.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", ",", "last", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Many you had one too many, the bronies (ph), what -- what dirty, shameful thing do you find yourself craving to eat?", "question_tokens": ["Many", "you", "had", "one", "too", "many", ",", "the", "bronies", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "what", "--", "what", "dirty", ",", "shameful", "thing", "do", "you", "find", "yourself", "craving", "to", "eat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I feel no guilt about pleasure, first of all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "no", "guilt", "about", "pleasure", ",", "first", "of", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You had a cronut?", "question_tokens": ["You", "had", "a", "cronut", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "You've -- you've had one?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "--", "you", "'ve", "had", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I've had a cronut.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "a", "cronut", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What -- what is a cronut?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "what", "is", "a", "cronut", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "So a cronut is a -- something we launched on the menu in (ph) May (ph).", "answer_tokens": ["So", "a", "cronut", "is", "a", "--", "something", "we", "launched", "on", "the", "menu", "in", "(", "ph", ")", "May", "(", "ph", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "So do you have -- do you cut the line at -- at Dominique's Place now that you helped turn this into a Frankenstein monster?", "question_tokens": ["So", "do", "you", "have", "--", "do", "you", "cut", "the", "line", "at", "--", "at", "Dominique", "'s", "Place", "now", "that", "you", "helped", "turn", "this", "into", "a", "Frankenstein", "monster", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I've cut the line twice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "cut", "the", "line", "twice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dominique"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "And I tell myself saying, if I could -- if I had a time machine, I would like to go back to 2004 and not have stopped, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "tell", "myself", "saying", ",", "if", "I", "could", "--", "if", "I", "had", "a", "time", "machine", ",", "I", "would", "like", "to", "go", "back", "to", "2004", "and", "not", "have", "stopped", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "CD", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yes, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2004"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130725pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "You would have kept going or you would have stopped?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "have", "kept", "going", "or", "you", "would", "have", "stopped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Oh, I would keep going.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "would", "keep", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]